macroplant.com 2016-10-27

# Macroplant - iExplorer License Agreement

Macroplant LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to Macroplant's commitment to protecting your privacy. Macroplant will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. 

## What information do we collect and what do we use it for?

We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. This information may be used personalize your website experience, improve our customer service or improve our website. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. We may occasionally send an e-mail notifying our customers of new products or protions. These e-mails may be easily opted-out of with one click. 

## Third Party Credit Card Processing

Depending on the product, Macroplant software can be purchased through two seperate channels. Most of our products are sold through our online store. These purchasess are securely processed using by FastSpring Inc. When purchasing our software, the transaction will occur on a secure site maintained and operated by FastSpring. Your credit card information may be required and transmitted securely through FastSpring in order to complete a purchase of our software, but at no time will your credit card information be made available to Macroplant LLC. For more information, visit [www.fastspring.com](http://www.fastspring.com/). 

Alternatively, our products such as itDJ and Awesome Files, are sold exclusively through Apple's App Stores for iOS and Mac. 

## Software Activation

Our products that are purchased in the Mac or iTunes App Stores (itDJ & Awesome Files) are activated immediately upon installation. 

For products purchased through our online store, upon completion of the registration of our software, our servers are notified of the registration code which was entered. In the event that we determine a particular registration code has been used in excess of the number of times that it is licensed, we may remotely deactivate the license code, thereby preventing it from being used to activate the software on additional computers. For additional information or concerns, please contact support@macroplant.com. 

## About Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages. 

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy. 

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

www.macroplant.com  
114 E Louisiana St.  
McKinney, Texas 75089  
United States

support@macroplant.com
